

Nothing defines success better than the self-satisfaction which comes from the work. Years of studies and its practical implementation at work has improved my understanding of design's relation to communication. And on that base has done multiple design projects which satisfied my creative hunger.

With an eye for perfection and attention to detail, efficiency, sincerity, hard work are my USP.

Beneficial knowledge of printing procedures adds as assets to my experience.

WORK PORTFOLIO: www.behance.net/JayeshC

WORK EXPERIENCE

June 2014 to Current	STERLITE TECH Associate Manager - Graphic Design	Creating Event Campaign, Brochure, Advertisements, UX/UI, E-mailers, Corporate Presentation, Animated 2D Presentaiton. Create elements for online marketing campaigns and design marketing materials for use in print, digital, and social media
June 2011 to April 2014	ELITECORE TECHNOLOGIES Sr. Graphic Designer	Provide visual solutions from conceptualization and design to production and quality assurance. Creating Event Campaign, Brochure, Advertisements, UX/UI, E-mailers, Corporate Presentation, Animated 2D Presentaiton.
June 2005 to June 2011	LIBRA MARKETING Graphic Designer	Gathered user requirements & creating Brochure, Flyers, Advertisements, Packaging
June 2002 to June 2005	AS A FREELANCER Graphic Designer	Designing brochures, flyers, book for multiple clientsPackaging

SOFTWARE SKILL

Corel Draw ★★★★

Photoshop ★★★★☆

Power Point ★★★☆☆

After Effect ★★☆☆☆

LANGUAGES KNOWN

Gujarati ★★★★

Hindi ★★★★★

English ★★★☆☆

EDUCATION

DIPLOMA IN FINE ART YEAR 2002

HOBBIES

Drawing Reading

BIRTH DATE

3rd December 1981

CONTACT

20, New Vandana So., Nr. Akhabarnagar Underbridge, Ahmedabad - 380 013.

+91 98242 27599 jayeshdesigner81@gmail.com